pearsonlongman.com 2008-12-16

# Pearson Education - Privacy notice

| 

Pearson Education Limited (incorporating Longman, Addison-Wesley and Prentice Hall) is committed to protecting your privacy. 

Pearson Education Limited collects personal information from you (by cookie technology- see below) through the use of order forms and every time you e-mail us your details, post a message to a bulletin board or provide shipping and billing information for an online purchase.

This Website creates a cookie (a small piece of computer code) which is sent to and stored on your computer containing a unique session identifier only. This identifier is used to record site usage statistics. In a separate automatic operation the web server will collect your IP address and details of the Website where you came from before entering this Website. This information is used to:

  1. work out how many times this Website has been visited; 
  2. record which parts of the Website have been visited so we can improve the content and layout of the Website. 

The information collected is stored on your computer and will automatically be deleted if you do not revisit this Website for 90 days.

If you do not agree to this Website's use of cookies you will need to disable cookies in your web browser settings - in doing so you may experience some loss of functionality while browsing the Website, particularly related to the online shopping basket.

Any personal information you provide while visiting this Website is confidential, and only used for the purposes described below. We guarantee never to sell Personal Information or share that information with third parties unrelated to Pearson Education Limited (or any associated companies which may be located outside the European Union) without your express permission, except to any third party suppliers we engage to develop or host the site or pursuant to any properly executed court order from a competent jurisdiction or if otherwise required to do so by law. 

Personal Information is: your name, phone number, contact details, date of birth, job, course information, recommended text, personal interests, credit card information, e-mail address, shopping selections and data about the pages you visit on this site. This may be used by us to process your online purchases, to inform you about other products and services, to improve the products and services we offer or for other marketing or statistical purposes and otherwise to better meet the needs and preferences of our customers. If you would like to receive any further information on other products and services, please send an e-mail to [webmaster@pearsoned.co.uk](mailto:webmaster@pearsoned.co.uk). 

Users should be reminded that any Personal Information that is voluntarily posted by a user to a public area of the Website, such as a bulletin board, may be collected and used by others. We cannot prevent such uses. 

When you place orders through this site or access your account information, we automatically send you to a secure server, provided your browser accepts Secure Sockets Layer encryption. In addition, as required by the Data Protection Acts of 1984 and 1998, we endeavour to prevent unauthorised access to the information through strict security procedures regarding its storage and disclosure. 

Our cookies do not contain any personal information, but they do enable us to provide the ability to store items in your shopping basket while browsing. They expire when you leave the site.

Through your use of this site, you consent to the above policy regarding use and collection of your Personal Information by Pearson Education Limited. Any changes to the policy will be posted on this page. 

This Website is hosted on a server in the EU or the US. If you have any questions in relation to the above, please do not hesitate to contact us at 

Pearson Education,   
Edinburgh Gate,   
Harlow, Essex,   
CM20 2JE

marked for the attention of the Webmaster.
